[light acoustic music]
[group gasping]
- It's finally done.
Our new house is complete!
Looking at it now, it is huge.
- Keep on digging deeper!
We're going to add a cellar!
- You want me to keep going?
- We need giant
support beams, too.
- And here comes the swing.
Fore!
Yep. I had an inkling it
would turn out like this,
but still.
- And Tia and I helped come up
with the new design.
Right?
- Of course!
We also addressed the requests
of the future residents
while you built.
- I'm a resident too, you know.
- It just wouldn't have
felt right, Hiraku,
if you didn't have
the nicest house here.
Let's tour the interior.
- [Hiraku] Whoa.
Looks a lot like the
house you live in, Lea.
- [Lea] Right now
we're in the main hall.
We designed it so that
everyone could gather here
and hang out.
And Hiraku, this is
your room here.
- Oh.
I like it.
- [Lea] And opposite your room
across the main hall is...
the dining room!
- This is impressive.
- [Lea] There's a kitchen
in the back.
We even set up
more stoves outside.
- So this is the cellar, huh?
This will be great for
storing food and firewood.
- [Lu] I was hoping for
my own room!
- It was getting crowded with
all the people we have now.
- Looks like you
like your rooms.
- Yeah!
- So what's this room
over here then?
This one has a bolt lock
for some reason.
Why did they put one here?
I'll pretend
I didn't see that.
- It's really exciting
to finally see
your new house like this.
- I love everything about it.
[Hiraku laughs]
- Looking up at
that tree from here
makes it feel like
it's watching over us.
This house is great, Lea.
- Thank you for saying so.
After you've spent
the winter here,
I want you to tell me if you
feel any of its unsatisfactory,
so that we may fix it.
- As you wish.
There we go.
[Hiraku sighs]
In addition to my God statue,
I decided to make
some statues of my dogs.
I put them in front of the
entrances to the new homes.
Yeah. This is shaping up
pretty nicely.
[light upbeat music]
["Flower Ring" by Shino Shimoji
and Aya Suzaki plays]
- Hm.
This looks like
all the main ingredients.
- I overdid it out there,
and now I'm starving.
What are we eating
for our meal today?
- I'm going to try and see
if I can manage a new dish
we haven't tried.
- A new dish
we haven't tried yet?
- Yeah. It's a dish
called curry.
- [Lu] Hmm. I've never
heard of that.
- You're going to
try to make it?
Then does that mean
that this curry
is a difficult dish
to put together?
- Well, it can be easy, but
mastering it takes some work.
Usually you just add roux
to the pot and be done.
[both gasp]
- So that's the kinda stuff
you're into you?
- You savage!
- What are you talking about?
- Wow. I didn't know you planted
all these crop fields too.
- I've been working at it
bit by bit.
- [Tia] There are a lot of
plants here I don't recognize.
- Yep. That's because there
are a lot of plants here
that normally can't grow
in climates with snowfall.
With the almighty farming tool,
I can grow plants that
are really sensitive
to seasonal weather.
The almighty tool
really does it all.
Okay. Let's harvest the spices
we're gonna need for the curry.
First up is cumin.
- That's a cute sounding
name for a plant.
- It looks already dried out.
- Once the flower blooms,
the seed left behind makes
for a good spice and is most
responsible for curry's aroma.
- What a peculiar smell
this seed has.
- Next up is turmeric.
It's the thing that
gives curry its color.
The part we care about
is the root,
but the part that grows
above ground is pretty huge.
We dry out the root
and use that.
- [Lu And Tia] Dry out, dry out.
- [Hiraku] I ended up
asking the girls
to dry them out for me.
- Become dry, dry out!
- Magic is really handy.
Next, is coriander.
We grind the seeds up
in the powder to use.
- This one has a nice and
fresh fruit-like aroma.
- Yeah. The green leaves up top
are an herb called cilantro.
These always have
a potent aroma.
[wolf barks]
[wolves panting]
You want to eat this?
Well, I guess we like
different flavors.
- Did you see that?
- Yeah. That's a plant capable
of driving off inferno wolves.
I think that one will be
worth researching.
- Next we have black pepper
and cayenne peppers.
Great! These are all
the spices I'll need.
Wait, hold on.
I heard that girls think
guys who make their own curry
from scratch are
a pain in the ass.
I wonder if that's really true.
[playful music]
All right.
This feels pretty authentic.
By the way.
Are you my only helper, Lea?
- [Lea] Yes. Lu and Tia said
they're busy with research.
They said something about
an all powerful
magical protection talisman?
- [Hiraku] Whatever.
We can handle it together.
- Yes.
[playful music]
- First, we start by heating up
rapeseed oil we extracted.
Then we go ahead and
add in the rabbit meat.
- Okay.
- While that's cooking,
we grind up all the spices
except for the cumin
into a powder.
- Is this enough for the meat
or does it need more time?
- It looks good.
Once you've got some
color on the meat,
take it off the heat
so it doesn't overcook.
Cook the cumin into
the leftover bits
and juices from the meat to
bring out the flavor and aroma.
Be careful not to burn them.
It's already starting to
smell like curry.
- Wow.
I've never smelled this before.
- Next, we need to focus on
sauteing the onions,
ginger, and garlic.
Smooth them around like so,
and then saute them
without burning them.
Now we add the diced tomatoes
and keep on sauteing everything.
- [Lea] Would you like
me to stir for a bit?
- [Hiraku] Thanks.
Once it's turned into a
nice paste, we can move on.
Spices in, boom.
We add salt, too.
Cook it a little more.
Then we add in the meat
and boiled soybeans
along with some water.
- It already smells delicious.
- [Hiraku] Now we let it simmer
until the meat gets soft.
- Do we just need to
wait for it now?
- Yeah.
We wait for it to cook.
I feel like I'm forgetting
something though.
What could it be?
[Hiraku gasps]
The naan!
- What is naan?
- It's naan, naan!
- It's naan, naan?
- [Hiraku] I was so focused
on the curry
that I forgot
about it completely.
Should I just make rice?
No. I want naan with this curry.
How many portions
do I need to make?
Me, Lu, Tia.
And if I add the elves, that
makes, well, it makes a lot.
It's the same recipe as bread
right up to where it rises.
The difference is that now
we roll the dough
out with a rolling pin.
- Right.
We're going to cook it now,
right, Hiraku?
- Yeah, that's right.
You're supposed to cook it
inside of the stove.
But I've seen people use
the outside of a pot before,
so we'll try that.
- What an interesting
little plant this herb
turned out to be.
- [Tia] It doesn't appear
to be poisonous.
- [Lu] What are they up to?
- I can smell
something appetizing
coming from over there.
And we haven't eaten yet today.
- Yeah, you're right.
- And here's the last one.
Great. And now for this.
It should be just about
done now.
- This is.
- [Tia] Curry, you said?
- [Lu] It's got a strange
color to it.
- [Tia] I'll need to work up a
little courage to try eating it.
- You don't need to be so shy.
I think it probably came out
pretty well.
You scoop up the curry
with the naan.
That's why it's flat like this.
Mm, it's great.
This is actual curry!
I can smell all the spices
throughout it.
- Oh, my!
This spiciness seems like
it could become addicting.
- The ratio of spices you use
changes the flavor, right?
This will definitely be
worth researching.
- Every bite I take makes you
want to eat even more of it.
- I'm so glad to hear you
all enjoyed it so much.
Well, it's got a
pretty unique taste,
so if you don't really like it,
there's no need to force
yourself to eat it.
Hey girls, would you mind
leaving a little curry
and naan for me too, please?
- Wow. It really does work!
- Well is is pretty spicy.
- I'm glad the
customers liked it,
but now I'm sold out.
This isn't the first time
it's happened.
- Wow, I'm stuffed.
- I definitely wanna
eat that again soon.
- [Lea] I've pretty much
memorized the recipe.
- [Lu] Let's change up how
much spice we use next time.
- [Hiraku] Well they
all liked it,
so I guess that's
what's important.
But still, eating just
a few bites of curry,
really makes you hungry.
Farming life...
- [Lea] ...In Another...
- ...World.
This year's winter
started to draw near.
Once the snow starts to fall,
we'll spend most of our days
inside the house.
We'll need to finish
our winter preparations
before that happens.
We should be all right
with this much firewood.
Hey! Zabuton!
I brought you something.
When it gets cold outside,
Zabuton hibernates at
the top of the tree.
Right. That's good.
I made sure to ask for extra
blankets ahead of time.
Thanks again!
We really needed these.
[hammer thudding]
Hey, good work.
- [Lea] You too, good work.
- Lea, along with the elves
are going to keep working
on the forge and some other
projects through the winter.
Huh?
I'm having Lu and Tia preserve
some food for the winter.
We season the meat,
then smoke it and dry it.
Kuro and the dogs won't
be able to hunt very well
during the winter
once it starts to snow.
That's why I want to stock up
on as much as possible.
[Tia yells]
Well, I think we'll be okay
as far as meat goes.
Right now, I'm working on a way
to preserve vegetables.
The vegetables go into
the boxes on top.
Then they're covered in a sheet,
and then we cover them
with snow.
It's called snow storage.
The bottom boxes collect water
from the snow to keep the
vegetables dry.
I'll try it out
as soon as it snows.
- Here I go!
I'm going to burn
all of you to ashes.
- [Tia] You're not
supposed to burn them!
- [Lu] I'm just messing around.
- I wish I could use magic.
[Hiraku yells]
Even though I knew it
wouldn't work,
watching them use magic
every day made me feel like
I needed to try it
for some reason.
I wonder why.
- Ignition may be
a low level spell,
but you still can't go and use
it without studying magic.
- Yeah, guess you're
right about that.
You all make it look so easy
that I just thought
maybe I could do it too.
I tried copying it,
but naturally, it didn't work.
- The golems Tia summons
are difficult to use even
among other magic users.
- [Hiraku] Then doesn't that
mean she's pretty amazing,
since she can summon a
bunch of them at once?
- Well, yeah, but I can do a lot
of cool magic too, you know?
- Of course, I know.
But still, you guys
are all amazing.
I'm glad that I have
you for help.
All I've been doing around here
is some garden work and cooking.
- What are you talking about?
You're the most
amazing one here.
- I am?
- Living out here like this for
as long as you have already,
that's not something
just anyone can do.
- If you say so.
- I do. No one's been able to do
something like this till now.
It's just you.
You're the only one that has.
- Really?
- Yep!
[light orchestral music]
- And so, winter had arrived.
The snow began piling up.
I think that's it.
We were spending
more time indoors,
so we needed things
to do for fun.
I started with
a classic, Reversi.
Then I built a chess set,
as well as a Majong set.
- Reversi?
- Yeah.
You play the game with
black and white pieces.
When you surround
the opponent's piece
you flip it to your color.
The game ends when
the board is filled
and whoever has
the most pieces wins.
Those are the rules.
- What a simple sounding game.
Is it really all that
fun to play then?
- How shortsighted of you.
It's the simple design
that allows
for complicated strategies
to be developed.
- You're right on.
It's amazing you know that
just from hearing the rules.
- It's nothing.
- Right!
I challenge you
to a game now, Tia.
- If that's what you desire.
After all, we've entered
a temporary truce,
since we started
living here together.
Then I suppose it's time
we settle the score.
- Let's try to relax some.
- [Lu] I'll be white.
- [Hiraku] That means Tia
gets to move first.
- [Lu] Uh... Then I'm black!
- [Hiraku] Fine.
This is definitely a win
for the white team.
- Oh no! My hand just slipped!
- Lu's the type that
likes to hit the reset.
- Sorry about that, Tia.
Since we don't know where
the pieces were,
we'll just need to start over.
[Tia grunts]
What's that look for?
[fingers snap]
[Lu whimpers]
- [Hiraku] Pressing reset
doesn't work against her.
- Don't you find it embarrassing
to use your magic like that?
- Not as embarrassing
as flipping the board
because you think you're
about to lose the game.
You haven't learned
your lesson, have you?
- [Lu] We're playing
the best of three!
- Fine by me,
I accept your challenge.
- [Hiraku] ] It looks nice
and peaceful over there.
[Kuro's paw taps]
- What, here?
Oh, you're absolutely right.
- You're amazing, Kuro.
- He understands the rules?
You're actually playing
the game right.
At a glance, this seems cute,
but I can feel a terrifying
energy coming from them.
I better not challenge
any of them to a game.
- Ah, is your game done?
I'm sure I'm not gonna lose
to the dogs.
- Lu, I don't think
that's a good idea.
- Come on.
What do you say we play a round?
[Lu whimpering]
- [Hiraku] As I expected.
She didn't have the courage
to press the reset button.
Hmm.
- Let's see.
- [Hiraku] Even Kuro shouldn't
be able to fully understand
the game of Majong yet.
It's far too complicated.
- [Lea] This one?
- [Hiraku] It might seem
a little childish,
but I'm going to take
revenge for Lu now.
Riichi!
- [Lea] Ugh, then I call tsumo!
No, wait, I mean ron!
- [Tia] That's ron for me, too.
At least I think so.
- Double ron?
Wait, the yasume should save.
Huh?
Me? What?
Are you kidding me right now?
It's the 13 orphans?
- Hey isn't this hand
the one they call yakuman?
- It seemed complicated
at first,
but the game is pretty simple.
- [Lea] Let's see. Hiraku
doesn't have any points left,
so Kuro wins the game.
- Kuro, you're number one.
I figured playing only board
games all day wouldn't be good
for our health, so I built
a mini bowling set.
- Good luck, Hiraku.
- I'm definitely not just mad
that I lost at Majong.
Come on!
[all gasp]
- Eight pins, not bad.
- [Tia] The arsonist
and the serial killer
are really hard to
take down, aren't they?
- [Lea] The scam artist up
front is real tough, too.
- [Hiraku] These nasty sounding
titles are ones we've given
to each of the pins here.
They were just normal pins
I'd carved at first, but.
- Why must we hit them?
- Lu hit me with that question.
So I decided the best answer
was to take out the bad guys.
[pins clattering]
Yes!
- I'm up next!
- I don't know if it's
because they enjoyed the
simplicity of it,
but the bowling was
a big hit with them.
And so we spent our winter
inside together,
nice and cozy
while playing games.
And those days went by faster
than we thought they would.
[food bubbling]
The snow melted and spring came.
What a lovely morning.
It's gotten nice
and warm outside.
- Good morning.
- [Tia] What are we
going to do today?
- There are a few things.
I just wanna finish
planting the crop soon.
I think it's time Zabuton
woke up from her hibernation.
We still have some
potatoes, right?
- [Tia] Yes, I believe so.
[hammer tapping]
- Based on the number of taps,
it should be coming
from this direction.
- Up there!
- Something big is headed here.
What is that thing?
A dragon?
- No, it's a wyvern!
- It can't be.
[intense music]
[wyvern roars]
["Feel the winds" by
Yui Hizuki plays]
[rustic music playing]